رَّبَّنَا إِنَّنَا سَمِعْنَا مُنَادِيًا يُنَادِي لِلْإِيمَانِ أَنْ آمِنُوا بِرَبِّكُمْ فَآمَنَّا رَبَّنَا فَاغْفِرْ لَنَا ذُنُوبَنَا وَكَفِّرْ عَنَّا سَيِّئَاتِنَا وَتَوَفَّنَا مَعَ الْأَبْرَارِ
	"Our Lord! We have indeed heard a call of one inviting people to Faith, `Believe in your Lord.' And we have believed. Our Lord! Forgive us our sins and write off our evil deeds. And make us die among those who are righteous."